[
{
	"question" : "what's that frog book lol",
	"type" : "regular",
	"answer": "The Winds In The Willows",
	"answers": [
        "The Winds In The Willows"
	]
},
{
	"question" : "By what name was the author Eric Blair better known?\nA) Aldous Huxley\nB) George Orwell\nC) Ernest Hemingway\nD) Ray Bradbury",
	"type" : "multiple",
	"answer": "B) George Orwell"
},
{
	"question" : "Who wrote the children's story \"The Little Match Girl\"?\nA) Hans Christian Andersen\nB) Charles Dickens\nC) Lewis Carroll\nD) Oscar Wilde",
	"type" : "multiple",
	"answer": "A) Hans Christian Andersen"
},
{
	"question" : "In \"The Hobbit\", who kills the dragon Smaug?\nA) Bilbo Baggins\nB) Gandalf the Grey\nC) Thorin Oakenshield\nD) Bard",
	"type" : "multiple",
	"answer": "D) Bard"
},
{
	"question" : "Which of these book series is written by James Patterson?\nA) Harry Potter\nB) The Legend of Xanth\nC) The Bartemaeus Trilogy\nD) Maximum Ride",
	"type" : "multiple",
	"answer": "D) Maximum Ride"
},
{
	"question" : "In Michael Crichton's novel \"Jurassic Park\", John Hammond meets his demise at the claws of which dinosaur?\nA) Procompsognathus\nB) Dilophosaurus\nC) Tyrannosaurus Rex\nD) Velociraptor",
	"type" : "multiple",
	"answer": "A) Procompsognathus"
},
{
	"question" : "What is the name of the gang that Ponyboy is a part of in \"The Outsiders\"?\nA) The Outsiders\nB) The Mafia\nC) The Greasers\nD) The Socks",
	"type" : "multiple",
	"answer": "C) The Greasers"
},
{
	"question" : "What book series published by Jim Butcher follows a wizard in modern day Chicago?\nA) The Dresden Files\nB) A Hat In Time\nC) The Cinder Spires\nD) My Life as a Teenage Wizard",
	"type" : "multiple",
	"answer": "A) The Dresden Files"
},
{
	"question" : "In \"Little Women\", which of the March sisters married Laurie?\nA) Amy\nB) Beth\nC) Jo\nD) Meg",
	"type" : "multiple",
	"answer": "A) Amy"
},
{
	"question" : "Which of the following authors was not born in England?\nA) Graham Greene\nB) Arthur Conan Doyle\nC) H.G. Wells\nD) Arthur C. Clarke",
	"type" : "multiple",
	"answer": "B) Arthur Conan Doyle"
},
{
	"question" : "What is the fourth book of the Old Testament?\nA) Genesis\nB) Exodus\nC) Numbers\nD) Leviticus",
	"type" : "multiple",
	"answer": "C) Numbers"
},
{
	"question" : "TRUE OR FALSE: Roald Dahl wrote \"Matilda\" after \"Charlie and the Chocolate Factory\".",
	"type" : "truth",
	"answer": "True"
},
{
	"question" : "TRUE OR FALSE: Victor Hugo's first novel was published in the 18th century.",
	"type" : "truth",
	"answer": "False"
},
{
	"question" : "TRUE OR FALSE: \"Life of Pi\" was written by Yann Martel.",
	"type" : "truth",
	"answer": "True"
},
{
	"question" : "TRUE OR FALSE: Jane Austen had eight completed novels published.",
	"type" : "truth",
	"answer": "False"
},
{
	"question" : "TRUE OR FALSE: Chinua Achebe was born in Nigeria.",
	"type" : "truth",
	"answer": "True"
},
{
	"question" : "Which book was famously rejected by 12 publishers before finally being accepted by Bloomsbury?",
	"type" : "regular",
	"answer": "Harry Potter and The Philosopher’s Stone",
	"answers": [
		{"answer" : "Harry Potter"},
		{"answer" : "Harry Potter and The Philosopher’s Stone"},
		{"answer" : "Harry Potter and The Sorcerer’s Stone"},
		{"answer" : "The Philosopher's Stone"},
		{"answer" : "The Sorcerer's Stone"}
	]
},
{
	"question" : "What is the name of Washington Iriving’s 1819 short story about a man that fell asleep in the woods for 20 years?",
	"type" : "regular",
	"answer": "Rip Van Winkle",
	"answers": [
		{"answer" : "Rip Van Winkle"}
	]
},
{
	"question" : "Who wrote the 1936 novel \"Gone with the Wind\"?",
	"type" : "regular",
	"answer": "Margaret Mitchell",
	"answers": [
		{"answer" : "Margaret Mitchell"}
	]
},
{
	"question" : "What was the full name of British novelist C. S. Lewis?",
	"type" : "regular",
	"answer": "Clive Staples Lewis ",
	"answers": [
		{"answer" : "Clive Staples Lewis"},
        {"answer" : "Clive Staples"}
	]
},
{
	"question" : "Who won the Nobel Prize for Literature in 2016?",
	"type" : "regular",
	"answer": "Bob Dylan",
	"answers": [
		{"answer" : "Bob Dylan"},
		{"answer" : "Dylan"}
	]
}
]
